<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Aitor Viana</title>
    <link>https://aitorvs.github.io/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Aitor Viana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aitorvs.github.io/blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Better merge commit messages</title>
      <link>https://aitorvs.github.io/blog/posts/42/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aitorvs.github.io/blog/posts/42/</guid>
      <description>I have used different code management systems depending on the company, from GitHub to Phabricator. But all companies have a very similar pattern:
 open a PR (Diff in Phabricator) fill-in the PR (Diff) template submit PR (Diff)  Generally developers put a lot of effort in the filling the appropriate information in the PR template, this is ours. And although templates may vary a bit from company to company, they generally all have the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to organize your gradle modules</title>
      <link>https://aitorvs.github.io/blog/posts/40/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aitorvs.github.io/blog/posts/40/</guid>
      <description>As your application grows, you hopefully organize your code into several gradle (library) modules. You can do that to isolate/decouple features, or to build common libraries for your code base, etc.
One pain point when starting doing this is that gradle modules tend to like to be in the project root folder, having a structure like the following:
- my-app | - feature-a | - feature-b | - feature-c | - lib-a | - lib-b | - lib-b This is a very flat structure for my taste, it would be much better if we could organize our gradle modules like the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why blogging</title>
      <link>https://aitorvs.github.io/blog/posts/29/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aitorvs.github.io/blog/posts/29/</guid>
      <description>Why blogging? this is a question that only recently, after talking to a very wise person, I came to a good answer for.
A bit of context, I like blogging. And at the same time, I struggle to be consistent about it. For the past years my blogging has been in bursts and pretty much I have always stopped because of the same reasons:
 frictions about the tooling to blog - see this for more insight on that I considered that the themes I was thinking about blogging were not worth putting out there  The second bullet above is the one that has been more difficult to overcome&amp;hellip;until now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Nth first blog post</title>
      <link>https://aitorvs.github.io/blog/posts/24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aitorvs.github.io/blog/posts/24/</guid>
      <description>This is the Nth first blog post for my (new) blog. My requirements for blogging are simple, I just care about writing and I don&amp;rsquo;t really want to waste a lot of time typing commands to create the blog, to format it, or publish it&amp;hellip;or any of that.
In the past I have tried several solutions such as:
 Medium &amp;ndash; I liked it because it pretty much meet my requirements, I was just concern about writing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
